Castañeda mss., 1950-1991 LMC 2719
Lilly Library
- Subject Files (Box 21)
  - Philosopical Method (Box 31)
    - Hector-Neri Castañeda, edited by Tomberlin (Box 32)
    - [Profiles: H-NC], (2 folders) (Box 32)
    - Burge, Harald Pilot, Helmut Pape (orange folder) (Box 32)
    - Semiotics of indicators, (3 folders) (Box 32)
      contains folder: German Semiotic Society
    - Festschrift, (2 folders) (Box 32)
    - H-NC: Spanish translation, (2 folders) (Box 32)
    - German Social Security Refund, 1990 (Box 32)
  - Personal & office files (Box 33)
    - Tumor, (4 folders) (Box 33)
    - Papers to write (Box 33)
    - Computer account - Aristotle (Box 33)
    - IU honor, 1990 (Box 33)
    - American Academy of Arts and Sciences, (2 folders) (Box 33)
    - H-N Castañeda award (Box 33)
    - NEH, 1989 (Box 33)
    - Photographs (Box 33)
    - NEH Sem. photos (Box 33)
    - H N-C: research report (Box 33)
    - faculty report, 1990 (Box 33)
    - Faculty reports: HNC, (3 folders) (Box 33)
    - Oral presentations (Box 33)
    - Castañeda, H-N., (2 folders) (Box 33)
    - Writing commitments (Box 33)
    - Donal Davidson (Box 33)
    - University of Arizona (Box 33)
    - Center Report (Box 33)
    - The National Humanities Center (Box 33)
    - [loose papers] (Box 33)
    - Papers on Reference (Baker) (Box 33)
    - [Curriculum vitae] (Box 33)
    - Castañeda, H N (Box 33)
    - [Loose papers - Who's who bio] (Box 33)
    - Castañeda's vitae, (2 folders) (Box 33)
    - Publications (Box 33)
    - H.N.C. Biography (Box 74)
    - software catalogues (Box 75)
    - miscellaneous (Box 76)
    - computer (Box 81)
    - Plato notebook, U. of Minn. (Box 83)
    - Retirement annuity files (Box 85)
    - my subscriptions, reprints, etc. (Box 88)
    - moral philosophy notebook, U. of Minn (Box 93)
  - NEH Seminars (Box 34)
    - [Loose papers], (2 folders) (Box 34)
    - Sitting chair, (2 folders) (Box 34)
    - Pavel, Thomas (Box 34)
    - [no label], (2 folders) (Box 34)
    - Pragmatism (Box 34)
    - [no folders put into 7 folders], (7 folders) (Box 34)
    - Identity: across worlds (Box 34)
    - [loose papers] (Box 35)
    - Pre-comments on books (Box 35)
    - C. festschrift - Tomberlin (Box 35)
    - Mahlon Powell - research assistant (Box 35)
    - Castañeda's meeting papers (Box 35)
    - Mahlon Powell - professorship (Box 35)
    - [Mahlon Powell] (Box 35)
    - Powell fund (Box 35)
    - Mahlon Powell - publication information (Box 35)
    - Mahlon Powell 75-76 MSP (Box 35)
    - Indiana University: distinguished professorship (Box 35)
    - Distinguished Professors (Box 35)
    - Center for Advanced Studies, (3 folders) (Box 35)
    - Noûs editorial board (Box 35)
    - Fac Res - HNC, (3 folders) (Box 35)
    - HNC, Sabbatical leave (Box 35)
    - [Sabbatical leave] (Box 35)
    - salary raise request, 1986 (Box 35)
    - H-N. Castañeda: Cinn. colloquium, 1979 (Box 35)
    - Castañeda - biography (Box 35)
    - Autobiography (Box 35)
    - Curriculum vitae, (3 folders) (Box 36)
    - NEH Seminars (Box 36)
    - NOUS, (2 folders) (Box 36)
    - Noûs Assistant (Box 36)
    - Noûs - comments, 1980 (Box 36)
    - Noûs exchanges (Box 36)
    - Noûs: service (Box 36)
    - Noûs: invitations to submit (Box 36)
    - Noûs monographs (Box 36)
    - Noûs office space (Box 36)
    - Noûs Indiana foundation journals (Box 36)
    - Payroll records & time sheets (Box 36)
    - Branman, Connie (Box 36)
    - Darosky, Renee (Box 36)
    - Dennig, Peggy (Box 36)
    - Noûs - cost and income, Vol VIII 1908 (Box 36)
    - Noûs: Acct. 21-305-56, 1971-72 (Box 36)
    - 21-305-56, 1973-74 (Box 36)
    - Noûs publication - Castaneda 21-3-5-56, (2 folders) (Box 36)
    - Noûs - Sustaining institutions (Box 36)
    - Noûs - sponsoring institutions (Box 36)
    - Noûs - subscription lists (Box 36)
    - Record of submissions (Box 36)
    - Noûs (Box 36)
    - Noûs: oddities (Box 36)
    - Noûs: Wayne State Univ. Press (Box 36)
    - NOOSE [sic] (Box 36)
    - [no label] (Box 36)
    - Desk, (2 folders) (Box 36)
    - Plato's Phaedo Theory of relations, (2 folders) (Box 36)
    - Non-justified justifiers (Box 37)
    - Participants (Summer), 1974 (Box 37)
    - seminar: papers, 1974; (2 folders) (Box 37)
    - Barnes, Ralph (Box 37)
    - Booth, Curtis (Box 37)
    - Coker, Horace (Box 37)
    - Davidson, Robert (Box 37)
    - Donaghy, Hugh (Box 37)
    - Greene, James (Box 37)
    - Murphy, Frank (Box 37)
    - O'Meara, William (Box 37)
    - Thomas, George (Box 37)
    - Vigoritto,John (Box 37)
    - Walberg, Hal (Box 37)
    - summer ethics seminar, 1974 (Box 37)
    - [no folders put into 2 folders], (2 folders) (Box 37)
    - Thinking and doing - (front page) Table of Contents - part pages (Box 37)
    - [no folders put into 8 folders], (8 folders) (Box 37)
    - SE Phil (Box 37)
    - [no label] (Box 37)
    - Thinking and doing, )3 folders) (Box 37)
    - Language and experience Un. Minn. Press (Box 37)
    - Philosophical methods (Box 37)
    - On philosophical method (Box 37)
    - Anderson, Kent (76) (Box 39)
    - Bethel, A.C.W. (76) (Box 39)
    - Fulton, James Andrew (76) (Box 39)
    - Gustavsson, Roger (76) (Box 39)
    - Johnson, Charles W. (76) (Box 39)
    - Lehocky, Daniel L. (76) (Box 39)
    - McArthur, Robert P. (76) (Box 39)
    - McCann, Hugh J. (76) (Box 39)
    - Price, Connie C. (76) (Box 39)
    - Quincy, Keith H. (76) (Box 39)
    - Smith, Donald L. (76) (Box 39)
    - Smith, John Leigh (76) (Box 39)
    - [ NEH seminar], 1976; (2 folders) (Box 39)
    - [ NEH seminar - corres.], 1976 (Box 39)
    - NEH summer seminar, 1976 (Box 39)
    - NEH summer seminar - invoices and charges, 1976 (Box 39)
    - NEH philosophy seminar, 1976 (Box 39)
    - NEH summer seminar, 1976 (Box 39)
    - 78 seminar "Trivial things" (Box 39)
    - Anderson, James C. (Box 39)
    - Baker, Lynne Rudder (Box 39)
    - Casullo, Albert (Box 39)
    - Crawford, Jeffrey (Box 39)
    - Crittenden, Charles C. (Box 39)
    - Heston, J. Clark (Box 39)
    - Johnson, Baylor L. (Box 39)
    - Lucey, Kenneth G. (Box 39)
    - McIntyre, Jane Lipsky (Box 39)
    - Panciera, Lawrence A. (Box 39)
    - Ringle, Martin H. (Box 39)
    - Rigterink, Roger L. (Box 39)
    - NEH summer seminar, 1976; (2 folders) (Box 39)
    - Summer NEH seminar, 1978; (3 folders) (Box 39)
    - [no label, (6 folders) (Box 40)
    - Dillworth, John B. (Box 40)
    - Foster, Thomas R. (Box 40)
    - Good, Robert C. (Box 40)
    - Kapitan, Tomis E. (Box 40)
    - Lee, Jig-Cheun (Box 40)
    - Lee, Steven P. (Box 40)
    - McDonnough, Richard (Box 40)
    - Miller, Arthur R. (Box 40)
    - Richards, William M. (Box 40)
    - Stephens, G. Lynn (Box 40)
    - Stiffler, Eric M. (Box 40)
    - [no folder] (Box 40)
    - [no label], (8 folders) (Box 40)
    - NEH 80-81 (Box 40)
    - NEH Seminar, 1984; (3 folders) (Box 41)
    - NEH Seminar report, 1984; (4 folders) (Box 41)
    - Louise Anthony (Box 41)
    - Mark Bernstein (Box 41)
    - Michael J. Costa (Box 41)
    - Dale Jaquette (Box 41)
    - Fred Hollberg (Box 41)
    - James S. Kelly (Box 41)
    - Josephy Losco (Box 41)
    - Frank McGuinness (Box 41)
    - Claudia Murphy (Box 41)
    - Paul K. Peterson (Box 41)
    - Michael Popich (Box 41)
    - NEH Brochures, 1984 (Box 41)
    - William Vallicella (Box 41)
    - NEH Alternates, 1984 (Box 41)
    - NEH applicants, 1984; (2 folders) (Box 41)
    - NEH Seminar NEH 80-81, (4 folders) (Box 41)
    - NEH Seminar participants' essays, 1982 (Box 42)
    - NEH Summer seminar, 1982; (4 folders and orange folder) (Box 42)
    - Anton, Antole (Box 42)
    - Ashley-Harmon, Lawrence (Box 42)
    - Blazer, Marvin (Box 42)
    - Buckner, Michael D (Box 42)
    - Fancher, Robert (Box 42)
    - Forrester, James Wm. (Box 42)
    - Forrester, Mary G (Box 42)
    - Kleiman, Lowell (Box 42)
    - Oetjens, John Robert (Box 42)
    - Swindler, James K. (Box 42)
    - Walker, Arthur (Box 42)
    - Zuniga, Joaquin A. (Box 42)
    - NEH Summer seminar General, 1982 (Box 42)
    - Bennewitz, Donald (Box 42)
    - Heberle, Klaus (Box 42)
    - Shoemaker, Robert (Box 42)
    - Spring, Jr., Arthur (Box 42)
    - Vorsteg, Robert (Box 42)
    - Keenan, Francis (Box 42)
    - Adams, Clifton (Box 42)
    - Becker, Carl (Box 42)
    - Brock, Jarrett (Box 42)
    - Bryon, David M. (Box 42)
    - Chung, Douglas (Box 42)
    - Connor, William (Box 42)
    - Crotty, Teri (Box 42)
    - Greenwood, Robert (Box 42)
    - Huston, Hollis (Box 42)
    - Janes, Royce (Box 42)
    - Laycock, Steven (Box 42)
    - Rusnak, Andrew J. (Box 42)
    - Skovira, Robert (Box 42)
    - Tominaga, Thomas (Box 42)
    - Ware, Norman (Box 42)
    - Oyarzum, Luis (Box 42)
    - NEH Seminar (Box 42)
    - NEH inquiries (Box 42)
    - Grim, Patrick (Box 42)
    - Anderson, Lyle (Box 42)
    - Chandonnay, LaVonne (Box 42)
    - NEH Seminar expenses (Box 42)
    - NEHSeminar applicant hist.[?], 1982 (Box 42)
    - Robins, Michael (Box 42)
    - White, Willie (Box 42)
    - Snakkowski, Edward (Box 42)
    - Rechtin, Lisbeth (Box 42)
    - Losco, Joseph (Box 42)
    - Loewer, Barry (Box 42)
    - Taylor, Kriste (Box 42)
    - Siderits, Mark (Box 42)
    - Summer seminar (Box 42)
    - NEH summer seminar, 1984; (2 folders) (Box 42)
    - NEH seminar reports, 1986 (Box 43)
    - NEH seminar (Box 43)
    - [ NEH Summer seminar], 1986 (Box 43)
    - report, 1986 (Box 43)
    - 86 NEH: essays (Box 43)
    - Kent Baldner (Box 43)
    - W. Stephen Corddy (Box 43)
    - Martin Dako (Box 43)
    - Lenore Kuo (Box 43)
    - Dennis L. Micham (Box 43)
    - James A. Montmarquet (Box 43)
    - James G. Mazoue (Box 43)
    - Lynn C. Pasquerella (Box 43)
    - Kirk Robinson (Box 43)
    - Elias E. Savellos (Box 43)
    - Edward S. Shirley (Box 43)
    - Mark P. Strasser (Box 43)
    - NEH seminar, 1986 (Box 43)
      contains folders: NEH seminar applicants 1986; 1986 seminar 3; no. 20 Morris, Katherine J.; NEH seminar Satro, Thomas W. #86
    - NEH seminar Timmons, Mark 30, 1986 (Box 43)
    - Grimm, Robert H. 11 (Box 43)
    - NEH Seminar enquieries (Box 43)
    - NEH seminar applications, 1986; (2 folders) (Box 43)
    - Ward, Andrew (Box 43)
    - NEH seminar NEH solicited reports of 1978 participants (Box 43)
    - NEH seminar application, 1986 (Box 43)
    - [ Summer seminars], 1984 (Box 43)
    - Hector-Neri Castañeda (Box 43)
    - NEH seminar, 1984; (2 folders) (Box 43)
    - materials, 1980 (Box 73)
    - Human Action (Box 74)
    - NEH Seminars, 1984 (Box 85)
  - Topics, A-Z (Box 44)
    - Abilities (Box 44)
    - Abortion (Box 44)
    - Abortion (Box 83)
    - Acquaintance (Box 44)
    - Acquisition Utilitarianism (Box 83)
    - Action, (2 folders) (Box 44)
    - Action (Box 79)
    - Action: explanation of (Box 44)
    - Action, Purpose/Oberlin Winnipeg (Box 79)
    - Action and Volition (Box 79)
    - Actions (Box 94)
    - Active-passive (Box 44)
    - Actuality (Box 44)
    - Adverbial modifier (Box 44)
    - Analogical argument (Box 44)
    - Analystic-synthetic distinction (Box 44)
    - Anaphora (Box 94)
    - A Priori (Box 79)
    - A priori knowledge (Box 44)
    - Approaches (Box 92)
    - Aquinas, Thomas (Box 44)
    - Argentenian literature (Box 44)
    - Aristotle I (Box 44)
    - Aristotle II (Box 44)
    - Arithmetic: axiomatization (Box 44)
    - Arithmetic (Box 44)
    - Arithmetic (Box 79)
    - Arithmetic: queer (Box 44)
    - Art appreciation (Box 44)
    - Artificial Intelligence (Box 94)
    - Asetiy (Box 44)
    - Athenian-Darwinian approaches to the history of philosophy (Box 44)
    - Attention (Box 44)
    - Atomism (Box 44)
    - Authority (Box 44)
    - Baker on Moore (Box 83)
    - Behaviorism (Box 44)
    - Behaviorism (Box 79)
    - Being (Box 44)
    - Belief (Box 44)
    - Belief (Box 79)
    - Belief (Box 94)
    - Bergmann, Gustav (Box 44)
    - Berkeley (Box 44)
    - Better (Box 44)
    - Black Culture (Box 44)
    - Bradley (Box 44)
    - Bressan, Alda (Box 44)
    - CA Repurzo Politico (Box 81)
    - Carnap (Box 44)
    - Castañeda, H-N. Comments on his action thoery (Box 44)
    - Casual diagrams (Box 74)
    - Categories (Box 44)
    - Certainty (Box 44)
    - Certainty (Box 79)
    - Change (Box 44)
    - Charles B. Daniels (Box 77)
    - Chishom (Box 44)
    - Classes (Box 44)
    - Closure (Box 44)
    - Cocchiarella (Box 44)
    - Colors (Box 44)
    - Communication (Box 44)
    - Concepts (Box 79)
    - Concepts, a priori (Box 44)
    - Conceptualism (Box 94)
    - Conceptual schemes (Box 44)
    - Conditional Deontic Logic (Box 79)
    - "Conditionals" (Box 84)
    - Conditions (Box 44)
    - Confirmation (Box 44)
    - Confirmation (Box 79)
    - Consciousness (Box 44)
    - Consciousness (Box 94)
    - Consciousness of Self (Box 77)
    - Conscious States (Box 79)
    - Content (Box 94)
    - Continued Fraction (Box 44)
    - Continuum (Box 79)
    - Conventionalism (Box 44)
    - Creation, human (Box 44)
    - Criteria (Box 44)
    - Criteria (Box 79)
    - Cybernetics (Box 44)
    - Das Denken und die Struktur (Box 81)
    - Decision Theory (Box 79)
    - Deduction, justification of (Box 79)
    - Defeasibility (Box 79)
    - Definition (Box 79)
    - Definition (Box 79)
    - Deonitic logic - criticisms variants (Box 44)
    - Deonitic logic (Box 44)
    - Deontic Logic, (2 folders) (Box 76)
    - Deontic Logic, (2 folders) (Box 79)
    - Deontic Logic (Box 100)
    - Deontic Logic (Box 100)
    - Deontic Logic, Robison, Anderson (Box 96)
    - Descartes (Box 45)
    - Description (Box 79)
    - Desire (Box 45)
    - Determinate-Determinables (Box 45)
    - Determinism (Box 45)
    - Dialogues (Box 45)
    - Disapproval (Box 45)
    - Dispositions (Box 45)
    - Donald Davidson (Box 79)
    - Dreams (Box 45)
    - Egocentrism (Box 45)
    - Elements of Logic (Box 82)
    - Elementary Logic (notes) (Box 92)
    - Emotions (Box 45)
    - Emotions (Box 79)
    - Emotivism (Box 45)
    - Emotivism (Box 79)
    - Ends (Box 45)
    - Ends (Box 79)
    - Entailment (Box 79)
    - Entailment and relevant implication (Box 79)
    - Epistemology (Box 79)
    - Essence (Box 79)
    - Ethical naturalism (Box 79)
    - Ethical theories (Box 79)
    - Ethical theories (Box 89)
    - Ethical Theories II (Box 93)
    - Ethical theories: Emotivism (Box 89)
    - Ethical theories: Hare (Box 89)
    - Ethical theories: Moore (Box 89)
    - Ethics (Box 45)
    - Ethics (Box 79)
    - Ethics (Box 93)
    - Ethics II: Ideal observer (Box 89)
    - Ethics--offprints, etc. (Box 45)
    - Euclidean geometry (Box 45)
    - Eudoxus (Box 45)
    - Events (Box 45)
    - Events (Box 94)
    - Events (Box 94)
    - Evidence (Box 45)
    - Evil (Box 45)
    - Existence (Box 45)
    - Existence (Box 94)
    - Existentialism (Box 45)
    - Explanation, scientific (Box 45)
    - Facts (Box 45)
    - Fatalism (Box 45)
    - Feldman (Box 97)
    - Fiction (Box 45)
    - Form (Box 45)
    - Foundations of ethics (Box 89)
    - Foundations of geometry (Box 45)
    - Foundations of mathematics (Box 45)
    - Freedom (Box 45)
    - Free will (Box 45)
    - Frege, 2 Folders (Box 45)
    - Future contingents (Box 45)
    - Hilbert's axioms (Box 45)
    - God: existence (Box 45)
    - Goodness (Box 45)
    - Goodness (Box 79)
    - Goodness (Box 89)
    - Goodness, propositions (Box 74)
    - Goedel's theorums (Box 45)
    - Geometry - perceptual (Box 45)
    - Greek Philosophy, (2 folders) (Box 83)
    - Guise theory (Box 81)
    - Guise theory (Box 87)
    - Guise theory Paradoxes (Box 45)
    - happiness (Box 45)
    - hare (Box 45)
    - Hegel (Box 45)
    - Heidegger (Box 45)
    - Helmut Pape (Box 77)
    - Hintikka (Box 45)
    - Hintikka, knowledge (Box 96)
    - History of philosophy: methodology (Box 96)
    - Holism (Box 96)
    - Hume (Box 96)
    - Husserl: phenomonology of (Box 96)
    - Husserl (Box 96)
    - Identification (Box 96)
    - Identity (Box 90)
    - Identity (Box 94)
    - Identity (Box 97)
    - Images (Box 45)
    - Imperatives (Box 45)
    - Imperatives: Logic of (Box 80)
    - Implication (Box 45)
    - Incorrigibility (Box 45)
    - Incorrigibility (Box 80)
    - Indicators (Box 100)
    - Indicators: "NOW" (Box 46)
    - Indicators: I (Box 46)
    - Indirect Discourse (Box 94)
    - Individuals (Box 46)
    - Individualism, sociological (Box 46)
    - Individuation, (2 folders) (Box 80)
    - Induction (Box 46)
    - Induction (Box 80)
    - Inference (Box 46)
    - Intentional Identity (Box 94)
    - Intentionality (Box 46)
    - Intentionality (Box 80)
    - Intentionality (Box 94)
    - Intentions (Box 46)
    - Intentions (Box 80)
    - Intentions - others comments (Box 46)
    - Interpretation (Box 46)
    - Introspection (Box 46)
    - Introspection (Box 80)
    - Justice (Box 46)
    - Justice; contract theory (Box 46)
    - Kant, (6 folders) (Box 80)
    - Kant: critique of judgment (Box 46)
    - Kant: ethics (Box 46)
    - Kant: epistemology and metaphysics (Box 46)
    - Kant is Imperfect (Box 94)
    - Kant's Apperception (Box 94)
    - Kant's Intuition (Box 94)
    - Kinds, natural (Box 46)
    - Knowledge, (2 folders) (Box 46)
    - Knowledge (Box 94)
    - Knowledge Analysis (Box 80)
    - Knowing who (Box 46)
    - Knowing that one knows (Box 46)
    - Knowing that One Knows (Box 80)
    - Language (Box 46)
    - Language, natural vs. formal (Box 46)
    - Law (Box 46)
    - Law and Social Philosophy (Box 74)
    - Law essays (Box 74)
    - Law, logic of (Box 46)
    - Law Rules (Box 94)
    - Laws, natural (Box 46)
    - Law: philosophy of (Box 80)
    - L. Bergstrom Alternative Sets (Box 83)
    - Leibnitz, (3 folders) (Box 46)
    - Leibniz, (9 folders) (Box 83)
    - Leibeniz (Box 94)
    - Lesniewski (Box 46)
    - Lewis (Box 46)
    - The liar (Box 46)
    - Life (Box 46)
    - Lingusitic acts (Box 46)
    - Lingusitics Acts (Box 80)
    - Linguistic structures (Box 46)
    - Logic (Box 46)
    - Logic (Box 93)
    - Logic #2 (Box 85)
    - Logic foundations of Utilitarianism, various chapters, (2 folders) (Box 93)
    - Logic (H.N.C.) (Box 92)
    - Logic of ethics, (3 folders) (Box 82)
    - Logic Materials (Box 88)
    - Logical Foundations of Utilitarianism (Box 89)
    - Logical, modal (Box 46)
    - Logic Entries in Encyclopedia (Box 80)
    - Logicism (Box 46)
    - Lorenzo Peña (Box 75)
    - Lycan-Boer (Box 87)
    - Man, human nature (Box 46)
    - R.M. Martin (Box 46)
    - Masochism (Box 46)
    - Material things (Box 46)
    - Mass nouns (Box 46)
    - Mathematics, bibliography (Box 46)
    - Mathematics, logic of philosophy (Box 46)
    - Meaning (Box 46)
    - Meaning: Twin arguments (Box 77)
    - Mechanism (Box 46)
    - Meinong (Box 46)
    - Meinong (Box 77)
    - Meinong Chishlov (Box 94)
    - Memory (Box 46)
    - Mental Representation (Box 94)
    - Metaethics (Box 94)
    - Meta-philosophy (Box 94)
    - Metaphysics (Box 94)
    - Michael Dunn (Box 77)
    - Mind-body problem (Box 47)
    - The mind; Oliver Sack's book copy (Box 75)
    - Mind-physicalism and others, (2 folders) (Box 47)
    - Modal Logic, (3 folders) (Box 80)
    - Modal Logic: Logic of Intentions (Box 80)
    - Modial Logic (Box 77)
    - Modality (Box 47)
    - Moore on Goodness - Katz (Box 89)
    - Monism (Box 47)
    - Montague grammar (Box 47)
    - Morality (Box 47)
    - Morality (Box 96)
    - Morning Star - Evening Star (Box 96)
    - Motion (Box 47)
    - Murder (Box 47)
    - Nagel (Box 47)
    - Names (Box 47)
    - Names (Box 87)
    - NAMES: proper names (Box 87)
    - Nature, human (Box 47)
    - new Plato (Box 87)
    - Nominalism (Box 47)
    - Objects (Box 47)
    - Objects (Box 90)
    - Ockham (Box 47)
    - Omnipotence (Box 47)
    - On Descartes (Box 76)
    - On Kaplan (Box 87)
    - Ontological argument (Box 47)
    - Ontology (Box 47)
    - Ontology (Box 85)
    - Ontology (Box 94)
    - Or (Box 47)
    - Ought: Kurt Baer on-- (Box 47)
    - Ought (Box 47)
    - Ought: Criticisms (Box 47)
    - Ought - is fallacy (Box 47)
    - Oughts and Moral Oughts, Austral J1 (Box 47)
    - Pain (Box 47)
    - papers on Indic. and Quasi-Indic. (Box 96)
    - Paradoxes (Box 47)
    - Paramenides (Box 47)
    - Particular (Box 47)
    - Perception (Box 47)
    - Perception (Box 90)
    - Perception (Box 94)
    - Perception (Box 96)
    - Perception (Illusions) (Box 96)
    - Perception (Linguistic Illusions) (Box 96)
    - Personal Identity (Box 94)
    - Persons (Box 47)
    - Phenominalism (Box 47)
    - Philosophy: nature of (Box 47)
    - Philosophy of the mind (Box 83)
    - Philosophy of religion (Box 47)
    - Philosophy of psychology (Box 47)
    - Philosophy of science (Box 47)
    - Physicalism (Box 47)
    - Plantinga (Box 47)
    - Plato's Greek (Box 47)
    - Plato's thoery of forms (Box 47)
    - Plato's Theory of forms - comments (Box 83)
    - Plato & Hume (Box 94)
    - Plato: theory of knowledge (Box 47)
    - Plato - moral philosophy (Box 47)
    - Plato: theory of relations (Box 47)
    - Platonism (Box 47)
    - Political Matters (Box 82)
    - Possible worlds (Box 47)
    - Possibility (Box 47)
    - Practical (Box 47)
    - Pragmatic implication (Box 47)
    - Pragmatism (Box 47)
    - Predication (theories) (Box 47)
    - Predicates (Box 47)
    - "Prediction" (Box 94)
    - Preferences: logic of (Box 47)
    - Presupposition (Box 47)
    - Privacy (Box 47)
    - Privacy Language (Box 78)
    - Private language (Box 47)
    - Probability (Box 48)
    - Pronouns (Box 48)
    - Pronouns (Box 77)
    - Proof (Box 48)
    - Proper names (Box 48)
    - Proper Names (Box 87)
    - Proper Names (Box 100)
    - Properties (Box 90)
    - Properties (Box 93)
    - Property (Box 97)
    - Propositions (Box 48)
    - Propositions and facts (Box 90)
    - Propositions, identity of (Box 90)
    - Propositions: Indexical (Box 90)
    - Propisitions and sentences (Box 90)
    - Punishment (Box 48)
    - Punishment (Box 90)
    - Putnam, Hilary (Box 77)
    - Qualities (Box 48)
    - Qualification (Box 48)
    - Quasi-indicators (Box 93)
    - Quantum Mechanics (Box 48)
    - Questions: logic of (Box 48)
    - Questions: logic of (Box 90)
    - Quijote, Don (Box 48)
    - Quine (Box 48)
    - Quine (Box 77)
    - Quine: translation, mind (Box 48)
    - Rapaport (Box 77)
    - Realism, scientific (Box 48)
      (emtpy folder)
    - Reality and language, etc. (Box 48)
    - Reasons for (Box 79)
    - Reason for Action (Box 74)
    - Recursive functions (Box 48)
    - Reduction (Box 48)
    - Reference (Box 48)
    - Reference (Box 87)
    - Reference (Box 90)
    - Reference de re (Box 90)
    - Referential opacity (Box 48)
    - Reincarnation (Box 48)
    - Relations (Box 48)
    - Relations (Box 90)
    - Relations: reducible to qualities (Box 48)
    - Relativity (Box 48)
    - Relativism (Box 48)
    - Representation (Box 48)
    - Representation (Box 94)
    - Religion, Philosophy of (Box 48)
    - Responsibility (Box 48)
    - Rights (Box 48)
    - Rights (Box 90)
    - Russell (Box 48)
    - Russian philosophy (Box 48)
    - Saul A. Kripke articles (Box 80)
    - Saussure (Box 48)
    - Schizophrenia (Box 94)
    - Scope Distinctions (Box 48)
    - "Self" (Box 88)
    - Self (Box 94)
    - Self (Box 96)
    - Self (Box 97)
    - The self (Box 48)
    - Self-consciousness (Box 48)
    - Self-consciousness (Box 85)
    - Self-consciousness & scope calculus (Box 81)
    - Self-identification (Box 48)
    - Self-knowlege (Box 48)
    - Self-ref (Box 87)
    - Self-reference (Box 48)
    - Self Theory, R. Cartwright (Box 85)
    - Sellars (Box 48)
    - Sellars, W II (Box 48)
    - Semantics (Box 48)
    - Semiotics of Indicators and Quasi-Indicators (Box 87)
    - Sense - Qualities (Box 90)
    - Sense qualities (Box 48)
    - Set theory (Box 48)
    - Set Theory (Box 93)
    - Set theory, Dana Scott (Box 94)
    - Shoemaker & Schonrich (Box 81)
    - Simplicity (Box 48)